MUHAMAD HAIDAR IJLAL

Karawang, Jawa Barat | +6285156203033 | m.haidarijl@gmail.com | Linkedin

About Me

I am a junior web developer with 2 year of internship experience in a university agency. Skills I have are Laravel, PHP, Javascript, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, MySQL. I am able to work individually as well as in a team. I easily adapt to various types of applications that will be created, this will make a positive contribution to growth your company.

Education

2018 - 2022

Informatic Engeneering – Buana Perjuangan Karawang University GPA 3.70 Thesis & Journal: Nutritional Identification of Apples by The Cany Edge Detection Method (Case Study: Fuji Apples and Malang Apples).

Links

- Portfolio https://muhamadijlal.github.io/portofolio/
- Github https://github.com/muhamadijlal/
- Instagram https://www.instagram.com/muhamadijlal /

Experience

Junior Web Developer

Universitas Buana Perjuangan Karawang | Karawang, West Java

10/2020 - 10/2021

- Find and fix various bugs on the website to maintain website quality.
- Collaborate with fellow programmers to develop new features that can improve application performance.
- Handle kinds of IT-related projects.

Junior Web Developer Training

BPPTIK KOMINFO | Bekasi, West Java

20/09/2021 – 28/09/2021

- User Interface Implementation.
- Implementing Text, Graphics, and Multimedia-based Programming Language Execution Commands.
- Organizing Functions, Files or Other Programming Resources in a Neat Organization.
- Writing Code With Principles According to Guidelines and Best Practices.
- Structured Programming Implementation.
- Use of Pre-Exisiting Libraries or Components.
- National Human Resource Development Strategy for Information and Communication Technology.
- Introduction to BPPTIK KOMINFO.
- Intellectual Property Rights.
- Identifying self-concept and its development.
- Preparing for the Job Application Process.
- Applying Effective Communication Skills.
- Cultivating Work Ethic.

junior web developer training and certification

BPPTIK KOMINFO | Bekasi, West Java

28/09/2021 - 22/10/2021

- User Interface Implementation.
- Implementing Text, Graphics, and Multimedia-based Programming Language Execution Commands.
- Organizing Functions, Files or Other Programming Resources in a Neat Organization.
- Writing Code With Principles According to Guidelines and Best Practices.
- Structured Programming Implementation.
- Use of Pre-Exisiting Libraries or Components.
- National Human Resource Development Strategy for Information and Communication Technology.
- Introduction to BPPTIK KOMINFO.
- Intellectual Property Rights.
- Identifying self-concept and its development.
- Preparing for the Job Application Process.
- Applying Effective Communication Skills.
- Cultivating Work Ethic.

Languages

Indonesian, English

Skill

Laravel, PHP, Javascript, HTML5, CSS, MySQL, Bootstrap.

Personal Project

- Dokumentasi arsip Universitas Buana Perjuangan Karawang
 - http://e-office.ubpkarawang.ac.id/
 - Laravel, MySQL, Bootstrap
- Data Vaksin Universitas Buana Perjuangan Karawang
 - http://datavaksin.ubpkarawang.ac.id/login
 - Laravel, MySQL, Bootstrap
- Report maba app
 - o http://datapmb.ubpkarawang.ac.id/
 - Laravel, Boostrapp, MySQL
- Laundry App Point of Sale
 - Laravel, MySQL, Bootstrap
- Kanemochi Point of Sale
 - Laravel, MySQL, Bootstrap
- Portfolio
 - o https://muhamadijlal.github.io/portofolio/
 - o HTML5, CSS
- Pusat Dokumen Fakultas Keguruan dan Ilmu Pendidikan Universitas Buana Perjuangan Karawang
 - o http://pusdokfkip.ubpkarawang.ac.id/
 - Laravel, Bootstrap, MySQL